Mighty Little Defenders 11 – New Wild Cosmos.
The Perilous Thorn Forest
Episode 6
Didn’t you say you could defeat monster?
monster come out to cause trouble again, it’s all your fault
I
See it?
We can’t defeat the monster at all
Giving Bulala is the best solution
Yes, yes
Someone better catch him
obey
Weslie
But without Weslie
Our losses may be even greater
Don’t worry Sparky asked us to wait here
There must be a reason
Weslie
Weslie, are you okay?
I’m fine
Thank you Spar—
Your Highness.
Don’t get me wrong
I actually have a requirement to save you.
I want you to help me find the legendary Golden Bulala
Golden Bulala
Father said
Golden Bulala is hidden deep in the Thorn Forest
Just finding it
can become stronger
By then
We can use it to defeat monster
There is such a magical thing
But
Why did you choose me to help?
Because I’m just like you
We both think monster is the key to all this
and
I admire your courage and responsibility to fight against monster alone.
Well, please let me go with you to find this Golden Bulala.
What about you? Will you come along?
Of course you want to come
If it weren’t for you just now
We would suffer
This adventure will definitely give you more courage
As you like
I’m coming too
Let’s go quickly
Otherwise my disguise will be discovered
Wolffy
After we complete the task
I will immediately find a way to restore your body
Okay
How to get in
Through my observations over the years
In the Thorn Forest whenever there is sunshine on a sunny day
The thorns will grow wildly
On cloudy days, the thorns will shrink back.
Then why don’t we come in the evening?
There will be thick fog in the Thorn Forest at night
It’s even more impossible to get in.
It turns out there is such a rule
Wait until the cloud covers the sun
We can use this time to get through the thorns
Then just wait for the cloud to come
Why don’t you sit with us?
I’m afraid he won’t be happy
What’s wrong with you
What is your relationship?
Could it be that he is your long-lost brother,
and you started quarreling over the future throne?
no
Not brothers
What grudges do you have?
enough
I say okay?
Ever since I was little, I have longed to get out of the palace
Frustrated by the rules of the palace
I can only stay in the palace all the time
one day
Whose ball is it?
Oops, I accidentally threw it in.
Why did you come out?
Are you playing ball?
Sorry for accidentally throwing the ball in
I’m the only one playing
Can I play with you then?
Okay
Is there anything fun outside?
There are so many
It would be nice if I could go out and take a look
Are you just pen pals?
When will we meet?
that day
What is this? Is it an assassin?
Who are you
Weslie Sparky
I see you said you wanted to come out and take a look
Then I, I—
Just like this we played together
No matter what we played at that time
we would always be happy
we became best friends
until
We came to the Thorn Forest
I want to find the Golden Bulala that Father told me about
Will you go in and find it with me?
I would like
And I will definitely protect you
The Thorn Forest doesn’t seem that scary after all.
Okay, let’s leave soon
wait for me
Why do these thorns suddenly grow so fast?
Sparky I’ll pull you out
it hurts
Sparky I’m going to find someone to save you.
Okay
I’m waiting for you
Weslie
Son, wake up
friend
the one who asked you to save me
how is he
who
No one is looking for us
we found you missing
We looked for you everywhere
Finally found you lying alone in a Thorn Forest
Weslie he didn’t come back to save me
Maybe there’s some misunderstanding there
At first, I thought he had some difficulties
But I just waited for his
that is
sorry
I won’t look for you again in the future
Since he chose to be
a coward who abandons his friends
Then I don’t have to cling to this friendship anymore.
You didn’t go back to save him
Of course not
Sparky and I went to the Thorn Forest
he was trapped
Please help me to save him together.
A noble prince would be with someone like you
and play in the Thorn Forest
Still trapped by thorns
Come on, go, don’t lie here.
We guard the city gate
We don’t know how the prince could have gone out.
Prince plays with you
Are you so timid to go to the Thorn Forest?
If no one helps me, I will save him by myself.
Where is Sparky?
I heard that someone took the prince to the Thorn Forest
It’s too bold, right? It’s fake.
I heard that he seriously injured the prince. Is that true?
What about the person?
He must have escaped
If I were the prince, I would hate him very much
I
I want to see Sparky
You harmed the prince and you harmed us and were punished
How dare you come?
Go go go. The prince said he doesn’t want to see you.
Sorry, I will never look for you again.
since then
We never met again
There might be a misunderstanding
You should explain it clearly in person
He won’t want to see me
But he doesn’t seem that angry with you now.
Otherwise, he wouldn’t let you follow him.
why don’t you be brave
The clouds are coming
quick
It must be when this cloud covers the sun
rush over
Let’s go
not good
Wolffy
Wolffy Wolffy, wait for me
I will definitely save you
save you
No
I don’t want you to get hurt anymore
Sparky
you
Everyone, run away
Fortunately, I have you
Bulala Weslie
What are you three talking about?
keep walking
three
He already considers you a partner
Then let’s move on
I am coming
To be continued